The Search for the Palace Letters is a documentary
film directed by Daryl Dellora.
This remarkable documentary tells the story of Professor Jenny Hocking, the historian who took on the
Australian Government and HM Queen Elizabeth II in a landmark legal battle - and won.
Self, played by Jenny Hocking.
Self, played by Tom Brennan.
Self, played by Antony Whitlam.
Self, played by Malcolm Turnbull.
Nuremberg (Russian: Нюрнберг) is a 2023 Russian historical drama film written
and directed by Nikolai Lebedev about the Nuremberg trials.
The script was based on the book Forever and Eternal by Alexander Zvyagintsev.
Nuremberg premiered at the Four Seasons Hotel Moscow in Moscow on February 20, 2023, and was theatrically
released in the Russian Federation on March 2, 2023, by National Media Group Film Distribution.
The film explores themes of letter, head of state, australian
history, british commonwealth, high court.